Lewis W. Douglas papers, 1859-1974 (bulk 1880-1960)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series IV: Lewis W. Douglas Papers, 1906-1974
  - Subseries V: Ambassador, 1947-1950
    - European Recovery Program, Germany (Lucius Clay). no date (Box 278, Folder 10)
    - European Recovery Program, Germany (various). no date (Box 278, Folder 11)
    - European Recovery Plan, Germany (Joint Report of the U.S. and U.K. Military Governors). 1948-1949 (Box 278, Folder 12)
    - Opening of Tri-Partite Talks on Germany (London). February 22, 1948 (Box 278, Folder 13)
    - Intergovernmental study group on Germany. August 1950 (Box 278, Folder 14)
    - England and Coal. no date (Box 278, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous Material, the "Vichy Gamble." 1947 (Box 278, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous Material, Monograph on the North Atlantic Treaty, by A. Thacher. 1949 (Box 278, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence (official), Attlee, Clement R. no date (Box 279, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (official), Bevin, Ernest. no date (Box 279, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (official), Churchill, Winston. no date (Box 279, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (official), Cripps, Stafford. no date (Box 279, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (official), Jebb, Gladwyn. no date (Box 279, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (official), Acheson, Dean. no date (Box 279, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (official), Acheson's visit. May 1950 (Box 279, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence (official), Harriman, Averell. no date (Box 279, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence (official), Kirk, Alan G. no date (Box 279, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence (official), Lovett, Robert A. no date (Box 279, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence (official), Marshall, Gen. George C. no date (Box 279, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence (official), Schneider, Franz. 1948 (Box 279, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence (official), Snyder, John W. no date (Box 279, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence (official), Truman, President Harry. no date (Box 279, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence (official), Department of State (various). no date (Box 279, Folder 15-16)
    - Correspondence (official), Department of Defense (including James V. Forrestal). no date (Box 279, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence (official), Economic Cooperation Administration (including Paul Hoffman). no date (Box 279, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence (official), miscellaneous. no date (Box 280, Folder 1-4)
    - Correspondence (official), McCloy, John J. March 1947-May 1949 (Box 280, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (official), Embassy personnel matters. no date (Box 280, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (official), Olsen, Lillian (secretary to LWD). no date (Box 280, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence (official), Sachs, Alexander. no date (Box 280, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence (personal), Office (Stroud, Morrison, Olsen, LWD). no date (Box 281, Folder 1-5)
    - Correspondence (personal), miscellaneous. no date (Box 281, Folder 6-10)
    - Correspondence (personal), regarding Douglas Family. no date (Box 281, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence (personal), speech by Mrs. LWD to English Speaking Union regarding Ambassador days in England. January 31, 1952 (Box 281, Folder 12)
    - Clippings. January-September 1947 (Box 282, Folder 1)
    - Clippings, Palestine Problem. February 1947 (Box 282, Folder 2)
    - Clippings, Secretary of State Marshall goes to Moscow. January 31, 1952 (Box 282, Folder 3)
    - Clippings. October-December 1947 (Box 282, Folder 4)
    - Clippings, miscellaneous personal clippings. February 1947-1950 (Box 282, Folder 5-7)
    - Clippings, Everybody's Weekly and Life. March 22, 1947 and October 27, 1947 (Box 282, Folder 8)
    - Clippings, World Topics Quarterly. Spring 1947 (Box 282)
    - Clippings. 1948-1950 (Box 283, Folder 1-9)
    - Appointment books. 1947-1948 (Box 284)
    - Appointment books. 1949-1950 (Box 285)
    - Events and Ceremonies. February-April 1947 (Box 286, Folder 1)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Pilgrims' Dinner (London). April 22, 1947 (Box 286, Folder 2)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Pilgrims' Dinner (London), commendations on speech. April 22, 1947 (Box 286, Folder 3)
    - Events and Ceremonies. May 1947 (Box 286, Folder 4)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Visit to coal mine (Yorkshire). May 19, 1947 (Box 286, Folder 5)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Propeller Club (Maritime Day, London), speech. May 22, 1947 (Box 286, Folder 6)
    - Events and Ceremonies. June 1947 (Box 286, Folder 7)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Fourth Centenary Clebration, Trinity College (Cambridge). June 3, 1947 (Box 286, Folder 8)
    - Events and Ceremonies, American Chamber of Commerce speech (London). June 26, 1947 (Box 286, Folder 9)
    - Events and Ceremonies. July-August 1947 (Box 286, Folder 10)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Canada Club speech (Dominion Day, London). July 1, 1947 (Box 286, Folder 11)
    - Events and Ceremonies, American Society in London speech (London). July 4, 1947 (Box 286, Folder 12)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Gauge & Toolmakers' Association speech (London). July 10, 1947 (Box 286, Folder 13)
    - Events and Ceremonies. September-December 1947 (Box 287, Folder 1)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Royal Aeronautical Society speech (London). September 9, 1947 (Box 287, Folder 2)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Imperial Defense College speech (London). September 9, 1947 (Box 287, Folder 3)
    - Events and Ceremonies, McGill Society of Great Britain speech (London). September 24, 1947 (Box 287, Folder 4)
    - Events and Ceremonies, American Society in London speech (Thanksgiving Day, London). November 27, 1947 (Box 287, Folder 5)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Pilgrims' dinner Honoring George Marshall (London). December 12, 1947 (Box 287, Folder 6)
    - Events and Ceremonies. January-May 1948 (Box 287, Folder 7)
    - Events and Ceremonies, International Chamber of Commerce speech (London). February 24, 1948 (Box 287, Folder 8)
    - Events and Ceremonies, University Club speech (New York). March 27, 1948 (Box 287, Folder 9)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Roosevelt Memorial Unveiling speech (Grosvenor Square, London). April 12, 1948 (Box 287, Folder 10-11)
    - Events and Ceremonies, University of Leeds, Honorary degree and acceptance speech (Leeds). May 7, 1948 (Box 287, Folder 12)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Presentation of U.S. Medals of Merit to Sir A. Fleming, Sir H. Florey, and Sir E. Herbert (London). May 18, 1948 (Box 287, Folder 13)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Council of the American Memorial Chapel Fund speech (St. Paul's, London). May 19, 1948 (Box 287, Folder 14)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Foreign Press Association speech (London). May 27, 1948 (Box 287, Folder 15)
    - Events and Ceremonies. June-August 1948 (Box 287, Folder 16)
    - Events and Ceremonies, University of Oxford, Brasenose College, Honorary Degree (Oxford). June 23, 1948 (Box 287, Folder 17)
    - Events and Ceremonies, American Society in London speech (London). July 5, 1948 (Box 287, Folder 18)
    - Events and Ceremonies, McGill Society of Great Britain speech (London). July 29, 1948 (Box 287, Folder 19)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Olympic games (London). July-August 1948 (Box 287, Folder 20)
    - Events and Ceremonies. September-October 1948 (Box 288, Folder 1)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Freedom House, N.Y., Anniversary speech (radio from Paris). October 10, 1948 (Box 288, Folder 2)
    - Events and Ceremonies, El Alamein Reunion with Montgomery speech (London). October 22, 1948 (Box 288, Folder 3)
    - Events and Ceremonies. November-December 1948 (Box 288, Folder 4)
    - Events and Ceremonies, "Pageant of Production" speech (Sheffield). November 17, 1948 (Box 288, Folder 5)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Universityof London Foundation Day (London). November 18, 1948 (Box 288, Folder 6)
    - Events and Ceremonies, American Society of London speech (Thanksgiving Day, London). November 25, 1948 (Box 288, Folder 7)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Simpson Services Club (London). December 14, 1948 (Box 288, Folder 8)
    - Events and Ceremonies. January-September 1949 (Box 288, Folder 9)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Imperial Defense College speech (London). March 23, 1949 (Box 288, Folder 10)
    - Events and Ceremonies, University of St. Andrews, Honorary Degree (St. Andrews, Scotland). June 30, 1949 (Box 288, Folder 11)
    - Events and Ceremonies, American Society in London speech (London). July 4, 1949 (Box 288, Folder 12)
    - Events and Ceremonies, St. George's School speech (Harpenden). July 22, 1949 (Box 288, Folder 13)
    - Events and Ceremonies. October-December 1949 (Box 289, Folder 1)
    - Events and Ceremonies, University of Bristol, Honorary Degree (Bristol). October 19, 1949 (Box 289, Folder 2)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Trip to Manchester (plans and correspondence). October 26-28, 1949 (Box 289, Folder 3)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Trip to Manchester (speech). October 27, 1949 (Box 289, Folder 4)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Trip to Manchester (miscellaneous material and album of photographs). October 26-28, 1949 (Box 289, Folder 5)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Middlesex Hospital, Prize-giving at School of Nursing speech (London). November 2, 1949 (Box 289, Folder 6)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Visit to U.S.S. Columbus with his Majesty (Portsmouth). November 8, 1949 (Box 289, Folder 7)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Visit to St. Paul's Cathederal (London). November 22, 1949 (Box 289, Folder 8)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Bristol Grammar School speech (Bristol). November 22, 1949 (Box 289, Folder 9)
    - Events and Ceremonies, American Society in London speech (Thanksgiving Day, London). November 24, 1949 (Box 289, Folder 10)
    - Events and Ceremonies, University of London Foundation Day, Honorary Degree (London). November 29, 1949 (Box 289, Folder 11)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Scottish Aviation Dinner speech (Prestwick, Scotland). November 29, 1949 (Box 289, Folder 12)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Royal Society speech (London). November 30, 1949 (Box 289, Folder 13)
    - Events and Ceremonies. January-June 1950 (Box 290, Folder 1)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Imperial Defense College speech (London). April 3, 1950 (Box 290, Folder 2)
    - Events and Ceremonies, National War College speech (London). April 18, 1950 (Box 290, Folder 3)
    - Events and Ceremonies, U.S.-British Fellowship speech (London). April 19, 1950 (Box 290, Folder 4)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Shakespeare Festival speech (Stratfor-Upon-Avon). April 22, 1950 (Box 290, Folder 5)
    - Events and Ceremonies, University of Birmingham, Honorary Degree (Birmingham). May 5, 1950 (Box 290, Folder 6)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Pilgrims' Dinner for Dean Acheson (London). May 10, 1950 (Box 290, Folder 7)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Annual Assembly of the Church of Scotland speech (Edinburgh). May 25, 1950 (Box 290, Folder 8)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Visist to the H.M.S. Victory (Portsmouth). June 13, 1950 (Box 290, Folder 9)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Sedbergh School speech (Sedbergh). June 17, 1950 (Box 290, Folder 10)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Universityof Glasgow Commemoration Day, Honorary Degree and speech (Glasgow, Scotland). June 21, 1950 (Box 290, Folder 11)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Royal Hoghland Agricultural Show (Paisley, Scotland). June 22, 1950 (Box 290, Folder 12)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Allies Welcome Committee Reception speech (London). June 26, 1950 (Box 290, Folder 13)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Australia Club speech (London). June 28, 1950 (Box 290, Folder 14)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Canada Club speech (Dominion Day, London). June 30, 1950 (Box 290, Folder 15)
    - Events and Ceremonies. July 1950 (Box 291, Folder 1)
    - Events and Ceremonies, American Society in London speech (London). July 4, 1950 (Box 291, Folder 2)
    - Events and Ceremonies, 16th International Congress of Ophthalmology speech (London). July 20, 1950 (Box 291, Folder 3)
    - Events and Ceremonies, "Freedom Bell" Casting speech (Croydon). July 27, 1950 (Box 291, Folder 4)
    - Events and Ceremonies. August-November 1950 (Box 291, Folder 5)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Royal Empire Society speech (London). October 19, 1950 (Box 291, Folder 6)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Tour of Third Air Division Bases (various). August 4, 1950 (Box 291, Folder 7)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Thirty club of London speech (London). September 26, 1950 (Box 291, Folder 8)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Presentation of Magnet to Southhampton Eye hospital (Southhampton). October 6, 1950 (Box 291, Folder 9)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Fly Fishers' Club speech (London). October 19, 1950 (Box 291, Folder 10)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Pilgrims' Dinner for LWD, speech (London). November 6, 1950 (Box 291, Folder 11-12)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Edinburgh Festival (correspondence). August 1950 (Box 292, Folder 1)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Edinburgh Festival (schedules and arrangements). August 1950 (Box 292, Folder 2)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Edinburgh Festival (22nd International P.E.N. congress, speech). August 19, 1950 (Box 292, Folder 3)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Edinburgh Festival (opening ceremonies, St. Gile's Cathedral). August 21, 1950 (Box 292, Folder 4)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Edinburgh Festival (University of Edinburgh, Honorary Degree and speech). August 21, 1950 (Box 292, Folder 5)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Edinburgh Festival (Freedom of the City Presentation to LWD, acceptance speech). August 21, 1950 (Box 292, Folder 6)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Edinburgh Festival (miscellaneous clippings and photographs). August 1950 (Box 292, Folder 7)
    - Events and Ceremonies, Edinburgh Festival (miscellaneous material). August 1950 (Box 292, Folder 8)
    - Invitations (declined), His Majesty's Government. 1947 (Box 293, Folder 1)
    - Invitations (declined), Embassies. 1947 (Box 293, Folder 2)
    - Invitations (declined), Dominions. 1947 (Box 293, Folder 3)
    - Invitations (declined), Armed Services (British & American) and related groups. 1947 (Box 293, Folder 4)
    - Invitations (declined), Art and Architecture. 1947 (Box 293, Folder 5)
    - Invitations (declined), Athletics and sports. 1947 (Box 293, Folder 6)
    - Invitations (declined), Business and Industry. 1947 (Box 293, Folder 7-8)
    - Invitations (declined), Charity. 1947 (Box 293, Folder 9)
    - Invitations (declined), Courts and Legal Societies. 1947 (Box 293, Folder 10)
    - Invitations (declined), Education. 1947 (Box 293, Folder 11)
    - Invitations (declined), International good-will groups. 1947 (Box 293, Folder 12)
    - Invitations (declined), International organizations and meetings. 1947 (Box 293, Folder 13)
    - Invitations (declined), local government. 1947 (Box 293, Folder 14)
    - Invitations (declined), performing arts. 1947 (Box 293, Folder 15)
    - Invitations (declined), press. 1947 (Box 293, Folder 16)
    - Invitations (declined), religious groups. 1947 (Box 294, Folder 1)
    - Invitations (declined), science and medicine. 1947 (Box 294, Folder 2)
    - Invitations (declined), social and personal. 1947 (Box 294, Folder 3)
    - Invitations (declined), U.S. (various). 1947 (Box 294, Folder 4)
    - Invitations (declined), miscellaneous. 1947 (Box 294, Folder 5)
    - Invitations (declined), His Majesty's Government. 1948 (Box 294, Folder 6)
    - Invitations (declined), Embassies. 1948 (Box 294, Folder 7)
    - Invitations (declined), Dominions. 1948 (Box 294, Folder 8)
    - Invitations (declined), Armed Services (British & American) and related groups. 1948 (Box 294, Folder 9)
    - Invitations (declined), art, architecture, and performing arts. 1948 (Box 294, Folder 10)
    - Invitations (declined), athletics and sports. 1948 (Box 294, Folder 11)
    - Invitations (declined), business and industry. 1948 (Box 294, Folder 12-13)
    - Invitations (declined), charity. 1948 (Box 294, Folder 14)
    - Invitations (declined), courts and legals societies. 1948 (Box 294, Folder 15)
    - Invitations (declined), education. 1948 (Box 294, Folder 16)
    - Invitations (declined), education (University of Glasgow, plans for Honorary Degree). 1948 (Box 294, Folder 17)
    - Invitations (declined), International good-will groups. 1948 (Box 295, Folder 1)
    - Invitations (declined), local government. 1948 (Box 295, Folder 2)
    - Invitations (declined), press. 1948 (Box 295, Folder 3)
    - Invitations (declined), religious groups. 1948 (Box 295, Folder 4)
    - Invitations (declined), science and medicine. 1948 (Box 295, Folder 5)
    - Invitations (declined), social and personal. 1948 (Box 295, Folder 6)
    - Invitations (declined), U.S. (various). 1948 (Box 295, Folder 7)
    - Invitations (declined), miscellaneous. 1948 (Box 295, Folder 8)
    - Invitations (declined), His Majesty's Government. 1949 (Box 295, Folder 9)
    - Invitations (declined), Embassies. 1949 (Box 295, Folder 10)
    - Invitations (declined), Dominions. 1949 (Box 295, Folder 11)
    - Invitations (declined), Armed Services (British & American) and related groups. 1949 (Box 295, Folder 12)
    - Invitations (declined), art and architecture. 1949 (Box 295, Folder 13)
    - Invitations (declined), athletics and sports. 1949 (Box 295, Folder 14)
    - Invitations (declined), business and industry. 1949 (Box 295, Folder 15-16)
    - Invitations (declined), charity. 1949 (Box 296, Folder 1)
    - Invitations (declined), courts and legals societies. 1949 (Box 296, Folder 2)
    - Invitations (declined), education. 1949 (Box 296, Folder 3)
    - Invitations (declined), International good-will groups. 1949 (Box 296, Folder 4)
    - Invitations (declined), local government. 1949 (Box 296, Folder 5)
    - Invitations (declined), performing arts. 1949 (Box 296, Folder 6)
    - Invitations (declined), press. 1949 (Box 296, Folder 7)
    - Invitations (declined), religious groups. 1949 (Box 296, Folder 8)
    - Invitations (declined), science and medicine. 1949 (Box 296, Folder 9)
    - Invitations (declined), social and personal. 1949 (Box 296, Folder 10)
    - Invitations (declined), U.S. (various). 1949 (Box 296, Folder 11)
    - Invitations (declined), miscellaneous. 1949 (Box 296, Folder 12)
    - Invitations (declined), His Majesty's Government. 1950 (Box 296, Folder 13)
    - Invitations (declined), Embassies. 1950 (Box 296, Folder 14)
    - Invitations (declined), Dominions. 1950 (Box 296, Folder 15)
    - Invitations (declined), "Invitations regretted." October-November 1950 (Box 296, Folder 16)
    - Invitations (declined), Armed Services and related groups (American). 1950 (Box 296, Folder 17)
    - Invitations (declined), Armed Services and related groups (British). 1950 (Box 296, Folder 18)
    - Invitations (declined), art and architecture. 1950 (Box 296, Folder 19)
    - Invitations (declined), athletics and sports. 1950 (Box 297, Folder 1)
    - Invitations (declined), business and industry. 1950 (Box 297, Folder 2-3)
    - Invitations (declined), charity. 1950 (Box 297, Folder 4)
    - Invitations (declined), courts and legald societies. 1950 (Box 297, Folder 5)
    - Invitations (declined), education. 1950 (Box 297, Folder 6)
    - Invitations (declined), International good-will groups. 1950 (Box 297, Folder 7)
    - Invitations (declined), International organizations. 1950 (Box 297, Folder 8)
    - Invitations (declined), local government. 1950 (Box 297, Folder 9)
    - Invitations (declined), performing arts. 1950 (Box 297, Folder 10)
    - Invitations (declined), press. 1950 (Box 297, Folder 11)
    - Invitations (declined), religious groups. 1950 (Box 297, Folder 12)
    - Invitations (declined), science and medicine. 1950 (Box 297, Folder 13)
    - Invitations (declined), social and personal. 1950 (Box 297, Folder 14)
    - Invitations (declined), U.S. (various). 1950 (Box 297, Folder 15)
    - Invitations (declined), miscellaneous. 1950 (Box 297, Folder 16)
    - Entertainment. 1947-1950 (Box 298, Folder 1-5)
    - Fishing, correspondence. no date (Box 298, Folder 6)
    - Fishing, invitations and trips. no date (Box 298, Folder 7)
    - Fishing, correspondence (miscellaneous). no date (Box 298, Folder 8)
    - Fishing, trip to Scotland, Laxford River. May 1950 (Box 298, Folder 9)
    - Fishing, clubs (Houghton Club). no date (Box 298, Folder 10)
    - Fishing, clubs (Flyfishers' Club and Piscatorial Society). no date (Box 298, Folder 11)
    - Fishing, LWD's foreword to Trout, by Ray Bergman. no date (Box 298, Folder 12)
    - Contributions. no date (Box 299, Folder 1)
    - Memberships, Allied Circle. 1947-1950 (Box 299, Folder 2)
    - Memberships, The Athenaeum. 1947-1950 (Box 299, Folder 3)
    - Memberships, City of London Club. 1947-1949 (Box 299, Folder 4)
    - Memberships, Honorable Society of the Middle Temple. 1947-1950 (Box 299, Folder 5)
    - Memberships, The Pilgrims. 1947-1950 (Box 299, Folder 6)
    - Memberships, Royal Thames Yacht Club. 1948-1950 (Box 299, Folder 7)
    - Memberships, Shakespeare Memorial Theatre. 1950 (Box 299, Folder 8)
    - Memberships, "One Great Hour" campaign for World Relief. 1948 (Box 299, Folder 9)
    - Memberships, various. no date (Box 299, Folder 10)
    - Trips, various. 1947-1949 (Box 299, Folder 11)
    - Trip to France and Italy. September-October 1949 (Box 299, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous photographs. no date (Box 299, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence (office), letters of introduction. no date (Box 300, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (office), letters of recommendation. no date (Box 300, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (office), requests for autographs and photographs. no date (Box 300, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (office), requests for articles, prefaces, reminiscences, etc. no date (Box 300, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (office), requests for messages. no date (Box 300, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (office), requests for various positions. no date (Box 300, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (office), requests for help on Visas. no date (Box 300, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence (office), requests (various and miscellaneous). no date (Box 300, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence (office), publications received. no date (Box 300, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence (office), publications received on economics, financial recovery, etc. no date (Box 300, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence (office), publications received (miscellaneous). no date (Box 300, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence (office), gift fo the Stone Griffin. no date (Box 300, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence (office), Gifts (various). no date (Box 300, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence (personal), Astor, Waldorf and Nancy. no date (Box 301, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (personal), Bracken, Brendan. no date (Box 301, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (personal), Brand, Robert H. no date (Box 301, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (personal), Brand, Robert H. no date (Box 301, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (personal), Clay, Henry. no date (Box 301, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (personal), Eden, Anthony. no date (Box 301, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (personal), Halifax, Edward and Dorothy. no date (Box 301, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence (personal), Esmay, Hastings Lionel. no date (Box 301, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence (personal), Jowett, William Allen. no date (Box 301, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence (personal), Leathers, Frederick James. no date (Box 301, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence (personal), Maud, John P.R. no date (Box 301, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence (personal), Simonds, Gavin Turnbull. no date (Box 301, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence (personal), Swinton, Phillip. no date (Box 301, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence (personal), Trenchard, Hugh Montague. no date (Box 301, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence (personal), Wavell, Earl. no date (Box 301, Folder 15)